const questions = [
    {
        question: "What continenet is the United States in?",
        answers: [
            "Africa",
            "North America",
            "Europe",
            "Asia",
        ],
        answer: "North America"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Lithuania in?",
        answers: [
            "Europe",
            "South America",
            "Africa",
            "Asia",
        ],
        answer: "Europe"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Lebanon in?",
        answers: [
            "Africa",
            "South America",
            "Asia",
            "Europe",
        ],
        answer: "Asia"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Mauritania in?",
        answers: [
            "Africa",
            "Asia",
            "South America",
            "Europe",
        ],
        answer: "Africa"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Iceland in?",
        answers: [
            "Antarctica",
            "Europe",
            "North America",
            "Australia",
        ],
        answer: "Europe"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Chile in?",
        answers: [
            "Asia",
            "South America",
            "Africa",
            "Europe",
        ],
        answer: "South America"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Brazil in?",
        answers: [
            "South America",
            "Europe",
            "Africa",
            "Asia",
        ],
        answer: "South America"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Malaysia in?",
        answers: [
            "South America",
            "Africa",
            "Europe",
            "Asia",
        ],
        answer: "Asia"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is Armenia in?",
        answers: [
            "South America",
            "Asia",
            "Africa",
            "Europe",
        ],
        answer: "Europe"
    },

    {
        question: "What continenet is San Marina in?",
        answers: [
            "South America",
            "Europe",
            "Asia",
            "Africa",
        ],
        answer: "Europe"
    },
]